Guide to the Daniel Nilva Negatives PHOTOS 067
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Other Clients.
  - Subseries VIII:B: Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Assocation]; Belt Industry; [Banquet at Hotel] Commodore, Oct 26, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1039)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Bronx] County, Oct 30, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1038)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Waldorf-Astoria, Nov 11, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1047)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Van Arsdale Dinner; Hotel Commodore, Dec 4, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1040)
    - Deborah Sanitorium WEVD [Radio] [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.], Dec 20, 1958 (Box 1, Item 736)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Waldorf-Astoria [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.], Dec 21, 1958 (Box 1, Item 737)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Ehler's Coffee [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.], Jan 29, 1959 (Box 1, Item 738)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Jacob Weiss Returns to Israel [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.], Mar 10, 1959 (Box 1, Item 739)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Coffee Industry Luncheon, Mar 10, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1041)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Queens Chapter Meeting, Mar 26, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1042)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Mayor's Office, Apr 21, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1043)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Israeli and Mother; Headquarters; [Separated as Damaged]; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Jul 1, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1866)
    - DeborahSanitorium; Ehlers Dinner; [Damaged Negatives Separated]; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Sep 28, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1865)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Assocation] [Bronx] Section; Concourse Plaza; Sullivan Dinner, Oct 21, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1044)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Dinner; Belt Industry, Oct 29, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1045)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Conf. Grain Co. [?] [Award to Rene Fribourg], Oct 30, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1048)
    - Deborah Sanitorium Knitgoods Industry Committee, Nov 1, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1046)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Knitgoods Committee [Separated as damaged]; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Nov 10, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1863)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Police Donation; [Separated from Damaged Negs], Dec 18, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1861)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Copy Neg; Sanitorium; Thomas Mackell, [1960s?] (Box 3, Item 1071)
    - Deborah [ Hospital and Sanitorium] [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Poster ["Your Deborah Tree of Life … Give It Life"], Jan 8, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1053)
    - Deborah [Hospital] Copy Neg; [Separated as Damaged], Feb 17, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1860)
    - Deborah Hospital; Copy Neg; Head and Painting; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; [Separated as Damaged], Mar 4, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1859)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Annual Convention; Statler Hilton, Apr 25, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1052)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Proclamation [Mayor's] Stark[?], Apr 26, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1050)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Deborah Square; 4 Neg [Group of people poses on wooden platform erected at Times Square (with Hotel Astor visible in background) below a street sign that reads: "Deborah Square.", May 16, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1049)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Members Meeting, May 19, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1051)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Luncheon; Waldorf, Jun 21, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1055)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Rosenberg -- Quillers[Quillins?], Jun 22, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1058)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Astor Luncheon, Jun 22, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1057)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hosptial [Jewish Consumptive Rellief Association]; Wolf Testimonial Dinner; Waldorf-Astoria, Sep 29, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1059)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Commodore; Belt Industry, Oct 18, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1054)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Conc. Plaza; [Award presented to Abraham] Bernstein; State Senator [Community Service Award], Nov 19, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1060)
    - Deborah Sanitorium and Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Knitgoods Industry, Waldorf, Nov 23, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1061)
    - Deborah Hospital and Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Annual Affair; Waldorf-Astoria, Dec 18, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1062)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Jacob Hoffman and Wife; Exodus--"Rider", Apr 25, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1063)
    - Deborah Hospital and Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Mayor's Proclamation, May 1, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1064)
    - Deborah Hospital and Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] 34 Luncheon; Commodore, Jun 20, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1065)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Queens Village; Arthurs [? Autumn?]; State Senator Mackell, Jun 22, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1066)
    - Deborah Hospital and Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Abbey Rosenberg Dinner; Waldorf-Astoria, Oct 4, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1067)
    - Deborah Hospital and Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Belt Industry; Commodore, Oct 17, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1068)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Mintz; Ukranian Jewish Meeting; Woodstock Hotel, Oct 25, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1069)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Knitgoods Committee Meeting, New Yorker [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.], Nov 14, 1961 (Box 1, Item 740)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] 39th Anniversary Dinner; Commordore Hotel, Dec 17, 1961 (Box 3, Item 1070)
    - Deborah Sanitorium; Mayor's Proclamation, Molly Picon [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Apr 23, 1962 (Box 1, Item 741)
    - Deborah Hospital; Commodore, Molly Picon Table[?] [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] "Award to [Molly Picon]; M.P. Speaking; M.P. husband…...", Jun 21, 1962 (Box 1, Item 742)
    - [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Deborah Hospital, Queens Banquet; Sam [?sky] [Shots include three union officials receiving the Deborah Hospital "Heart of Gold" award certificates: Louis L. Levi, Jun 23, 1962 (Box 1, Item 743)
    - Deborah Hospital [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Fan] Ziskin, Jul 15, 1962 (Box 1, Item 744)
  - Subseries VIII:C: Leather Craft Guild.
    - Leather Craft Guild [?] 25 W. 53 St., [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 552)
  - Subseries VIII:D: New York State Department of Labor.
    - NY State Department Noah Walter, 80 Center [Centre?] NYC, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 930)
  - Subseries VIII:E: Produce Exchange.
    - Mort Lawrence, Produce Exchange, Interiors and Headshots, Oct 30, 1950 (Box 2, Item 944)
    - Produce Exchange [party or reception], Nov 24, 1959 (Box 2, Item 946)
  - Subseries VIII:F: Rural Schools.
    - Rural Schools Luncheon, Hotel Commadore, Nov 19, 1955 (Box 1, Item 650)
  - Subseries VIII:G: WEVD Radio.
    - [WEVD] [2 men doing a radio broadcast?], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 598)
    - Political / La Guardia/Thomas Dewey/ Alex Rose/ Dewey & Antonini [WEVD Radio], 1938 (Box 1, Item 554)
- Series IX: Personal.
  - H. Fox Frances and Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva, Daniel Nilva's first wife], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 668)
  - Mildred [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva] at Piano, Dec 1, 1939 (Box 1, Item 665)
  - Mildred Nilva [copy shot of image of Mildred Nilva as a young girl], [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 666)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 664)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva, ] [Outside (?) Summer Portraits], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 663)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 662)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 661)
  - Millie [Nilva?] [Portrait with 3 other women and 1 man], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 659)
  - Edie, Jimmy, Dan [Nilva?], Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 658)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 657)
  - Dan [Nilva?], Edie, Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], Jimmy, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 656)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 655)
  - Millie [probably Alice "Millie" Nilva] [copy shot of letter written in French], Sep 7, 1949 (Box 1, Item 667)
  - Self [Daniel Nilva?] and Drh[?] [Possibly Daniel Nilva, and dog; Portrait: unidentified man -- "Drh"?], [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 660)
- Series X: Unprocessed Materials (Box 5, Box 6)
  - Unprocessed 35mm, 120, 2 1/4, and 4 x 5 negatives. (Box 5)
  - Unprocessed 5 x 7 and 8 x 10 Negatives (Box 6)